

Chukwuemeka Remigius

Fullstack Javascript and Solidity Programmer.

Email: chuksremi15@gmail.com Phone: +2348160564759

Github: https://github.com/chuksremi15 Portfolio: https://chuksremyblog.web.app

Driven professional with a broad technical skill set. Excellent communicator experienced in interpreting and implementing client and staff vision of new websites and programs. Known for ability to multitask and juggle multiple pressing projects simultaneously, meeting all deadlines. Thrives in environments that constantly embrace new technologies.

譜 **Technical Skills**

Node.js	3 years	
React	3 years	
Solidity	1 years	
Typescript	3 years	
Redux	3 years	

Additional skills:

Ethers 1 year	Firebase 3 year	Blockchain 1 year	MySQL 2 year
Hardhat 1 year	Truffle 1 year	Web3.js 1 year	Express.js 3 year
TailwindCss 2 year			

Work History

Frontend Programmer at Canary Tech

June 2019 - December 2021 | 2 years 5 months

Canary tech is the parent company of parapay, a fintech startup.

- Collaborated with a team of five developers in building the fintech app.
- Integrated Web API's to frontend Applications.
- Worked with Chakra UI, Sass, Redux-saga.
- Developed Admin front end using react and redux-saga for state management

The product has handled more than 10 billion naira in transactions leading to revenue growth.

0 March 2021 - December 2021 | 9 months

Full-stack Programmer at Midleman

Midleman is a med e-commerce start-up that provides healthcare products to hospitals, pharmacies and individuals.

team. Built core backend functionalities which include business logic that

Developed the software architecture blueprint that guided the rest of the

- satisfied the founder's description. Worked with services like Paystack, AWS, and Nodemailer.
- Built part of the front-end using React, Tailwind CSS, and Redux-saga.

The product has substantially bridged the gap between drug supplies and

hospitals. It is projected to provide quality and certified health products to millions of individuals, five thousand hospitals, and pharmaceutical stores across the southern part of Nigeria.

January 2022 - now | 5 months

Full-stack Blockchain Programmer at Omitch

Omitch is a casino game start-up on the blockchain

Responsible for the full cycles of the blockchain development which include

- writing smart contracts, writing tests, and integrating ABIs to frontend. Converted casino business logic to code.
- Integrated games from a gaming provider
- Worked with Hardhat, Mocha, Chai, Ethers, and Web3js.

Trading platform for a crypto trader

Side projects

NFT minting website https://www.teensnfts.art/

https://activetraderspro.com/



Education

December 2017 - December 2021

Nnamdi Azikiwe University

BSC in computer science